<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:background="#00704a"
    tools:context=".LeafRustMild">

    <!-- ImageView for the picture -->

    <ImageView
        android:id="@+id/imageView26"
        android:layout_width="449dp"
        android:layout_height="430dp"
        android:layout_alignParentStart="true"
        android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
        android:background="@drawable/whitebg2"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="0.0"
        tools:ignore="MissingConstraints" />

    <ScrollView
        android:id="@+id/scrollView2"
        android:layout_width="327dp"
        android:layout_height="351dp"
        android:layout_alignParentTop="true"
        android:layout_alignParentEnd="true"
        android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="340dp"
        android:layout_marginEnd="2dp"
        android:layout_marginBottom="40dp"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="0.936">

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="300dp"
            android:layout_height="600dp"
            android:fontFamily="@font/hammersmith_one"
            android:justificationMode="inter_word"
            android:text="Mild Coffee Leaf Rust disease, caused by the fungus Hemileia vastatrix, is a prevalent fungal infection affecting coffee plants. Here is a description of the mild form of the disease:\n\nSymptoms:\n\nYellow Pustules: The disease initiates with the appearance of small, yellow pustules on the undersides of coffee leaves, indicating the presence of rust spores.\nOrange Powder: As the infection progresses, these pustules transform into powdery orange masses, creating a distinctive rusty appearance on the leaf surface.\nLeaf Yellowing: Infected leaves exhibit yellowing, known as chlorosis, as a consequence of reduced chlorophyll production caused by the rust invasion.\nPremature Leaf Drop: In severe cases, the leaves may prematurely drop, leading to a reduction in the plant's photosynthetic capacity.\n\nProgression:\n\nExpansion: The rust pustules gradually enlarge and may coalesce, forming larger areas of infection on the leaf surface.\nSecondary Infections: Secondary infections can occur on new leaves, perpetuating the cycle of the disease.\n\nSpread and Survival:\n\nWind Dispersal: The rust spores are primarily dispersed by wind, facilitating the rapid spread of the disease within coffee plantations.\nSurvival on Debris: The fungus can survive on fallen leaves and other plant debris, contributing to its persistence between growing seasons.\n\nFavorable Conditions:\n\nMoisture: High humidity, especially during the morning hours, provides conducive conditions for the development and spread of Coffee Leaf Rust.\nTemperature: Moderate temperatures ranging between 20 to 25 degrees Celsius favor the growth and reproduction of the rust fungus.\n\nManagement and Control:\n\nResistant Varieties: Planting coffee varieties resistant to Coffee Leaf Rust is a fundamental strategy in disease management.\nFungicides: Application of fungicides, especially during the early stages of infection, can effectively suppress the spread of the rust disease.\nPruning: Regular pruning of infected branches helps remove potential sources of spores and reduces the overall disease pressure.\nCultural Practices: Improving plantation practices, such as maintaining proper spacing between coffee plants and promoting good air circulation, aids in disease prevention.\nRegular Monitoring: Routine field inspections for early detection of rust symptoms enable timely intervention and control measures.\n\nConclusion:\n\nMild Coffee Leaf Rust disease poses a significant threat to coffee cultivation. Vigilant monitoring, integrated pest management strategies, and the adoption of resistant varieties are pivotal in mitigating the impact of this fungal infection and sustaining coffee yields. Collaboration with agricultural experts and adherence to recommended control measures are imperative for the long-term health and productivity of coffee plants."
            android:textColor="@color/green"
            android:textStyle="bold" />


    </ScrollView>

    <!-- TextView for the description -->

    <FrameLayout
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="48dp"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        tools:ignore="ExtraText">

        <!-- White border -->
        <View
            android:layout_width="320dp"
            android:layout_height="220dp"
            android:background="@android:color/white"/> <!-- Adjust the width to control the border size -->
        <!-- Adjust the height to control the border size -->


        <!-- Original ImageView with content -->
        <ImageView
            android:id="@+id/imageViewMild"
            android:layout_width="300dp"
            android:layout_height="200dp"
            android:layout_gravity="center"
            android:scaleType="centerCrop"
            android:src="@drawable/leafrustmild" />
    </FrameLayout>


    <!-- Back Button -->



    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView43"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_alignParentTop="true"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="9dp"
        android:fontFamily="@font/hammersmith_one"
        android:text="Mild Leaf Rust"
        android:textColor="@color/white"
        android:textSize="25sp"
        android:textStyle="bold" />

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView44"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="300dp"
        android:fontFamily="@font/hammersmith_one"
        android:text="Description"
        android:textColor="@color/green"
        android:textSize="25sp"
        android:textStyle="bold" />


</RelativeLayout>
