<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:background="#00704a"
    tools:context=".SootyMoldCrit">

    <!-- ImageView for the picture -->

    <ImageView
        android:id="@+id/imageView26"
        android:layout_width="449dp"
        android:layout_height="430dp"
        android:layout_alignParentStart="true"
        android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
        android:background="@drawable/whitebg2"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="0.0"
        tools:ignore="MissingConstraints" />

    <ScrollView
        android:id="@+id/scrollView2"
        android:layout_width="327dp"
        android:layout_height="351dp"
        android:layout_alignParentTop="true"
        android:layout_alignParentEnd="true"
        android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="340dp"
        android:layout_marginEnd="2dp"
        android:layout_marginBottom="40dp"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="0.936">

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="300dp"
            android:layout_height="600dp"
            android:fontFamily="@font/hammersmith_one"
            android:justificationMode="inter_word"
            android:text="Critical Coffee Leaf Sooty Molds Disease, caused by various species of fungi belonging to the genera Capnodium, Scorias, and others, represents a severe threat to coffee plants. Here is a comprehensive description of the critical form of the disease:\n\nSymptoms:\n\nSooty Mold Growth: The primary symptom of Critical Coffee Leaf Sooty Molds Disease is the development of dark, sooty mold growth on the surfaces of leaves. This growth is a result of the presence of honeydew excreted by sap-feeding insects such as aphids, whiteflies, or scale insects.\n\nBlack Coating: Affected leaves become covered with a black, velvety coating of sooty mold, impairing their ability to photosynthesize and ultimately compromising plant health.\n\nSticky Residue: The honeydew excreted by insects not only encourages sooty mold growth but also leaves a sticky residue on leaves and nearby surfaces, further exacerbating the aesthetic and physiological damage.\n\nProgression:\n\nRapid Spread: Critical Sooty Molds Disease can spread rapidly, especially in conditions conducive to the proliferation of sap-feeding insects.\n\nMultiple Hosts: The disease can affect various plant species, emphasizing its potential for widespread impact in agricultural and horticultural settings.\n\nSpread and Survival:\n\nInsect-Mediated Spread: The primary mode of disease transmission is through honeydew-excreting insects. The molds thrive on the sugary substance produced by these insects.\n\nSurvival: Sooty molds can survive on surfaces, including leaves and branches, as well as in the soil, ensuring the persistence of the disease even in the absence of active insect vectors.\n\nFavorable Conditions:\n\nInsect Presence: The presence of sap-feeding insects, which create honeydew, is a prerequisite for the development of Critical Sooty Molds Disease.\n\nHumidity: High humidity facilitates the growth of sooty molds, emphasizing the role of environmental conditions in disease progression.\n\nManagement and Control:\n\nInsect Control: Effectively managing sap-feeding insects through insecticides or biological controls is a crucial step in preventing the development and spread of sooty molds.\n\nHorticultural Oils: Applying horticultural oils can help control the population of honeydew-producing insects and reduce the favorable conditions for mold growth.\n\nPruning: Pruning affected plant parts and maintaining proper spacing between plants enhance air circulation, reducing the conducive environment for disease development.\n\nConsultation:\n\nExpert Guidance: Given the complexity of managing Critical Coffee Leaf Sooty Molds Disease, consultation with entomologists, plant pathologists, or agricultural specialists is advisable to tailor control strategies to specific conditions.\n\nConclusion:\n\nCritical Coffee Leaf Sooty Molds Disease poses a significant risk to coffee plants and other susceptible vegetation. Vigilant monitoring, integrated pest management strategies, and collaboration with experts are essential components of effective disease prevention and control. Neglecting these measures can lead to widespread infestations, compromising the vitality of plants and agricultural productivity."
            android:textColor="@color/green"
            android:textStyle="bold" />


    </ScrollView>

    <!-- TextView for the description -->

    <FrameLayout
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="48dp"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        tools:ignore="ExtraText">

        <!-- White border -->
        <View
            android:layout_width="320dp"
            android:layout_height="220dp"
            android:background="@android:color/white"/> <!-- Adjust the width to control the border size -->
        <!-- Adjust the height to control the border size -->


        <!-- Original ImageView with content -->
        <ImageView
            android:id="@+id/imageViewMild"
            android:layout_width="300dp"
            android:layout_height="200dp"
            android:layout_gravity="center"
            android:scaleType="centerCrop"
            android:src="@drawable/sootymoldcritical" />
    </FrameLayout>


    <!-- Back Button -->



    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView43"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_alignParentTop="true"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="9dp"
        android:fontFamily="@font/hammersmith_one"
        android:text="Critical Sooty Molds"
        android:textColor="@color/white"
        android:textSize="25sp"
        android:textStyle="bold" />

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView44"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="300dp"
        android:fontFamily="@font/hammersmith_one"
        android:text="Description"
        android:textColor="@color/green"
        android:textSize="25sp"
        android:textStyle="bold" />


</RelativeLayout>
