<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:background="#00704a"
    tools:context=".LeafRustCrit">

    <!-- ImageView for the picture -->

    <ImageView
        android:id="@+id/imageView26"
        android:layout_width="449dp"
        android:layout_height="430dp"
        android:layout_alignParentStart="true"
        android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
        android:background="@drawable/whitebg2"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="0.0"
        tools:ignore="MissingConstraints" />

    <ScrollView
        android:id="@+id/scrollView2"
        android:layout_width="327dp"
        android:layout_height="351dp"
        android:layout_alignParentTop="true"
        android:layout_alignParentEnd="true"
        android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="340dp"
        android:layout_marginEnd="2dp"
        android:layout_marginBottom="40dp"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="0.936">

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="300dp"
            android:layout_height="600dp"
            android:fontFamily="@font/hammersmith_one"
            android:justificationMode="inter_word"
            android:text="Critical Coffee Leaf Rust disease, caused by the fungus Hemileia vastatrix, is a severe and economically significant fungal infection affecting coffee plants. Here is a description of the critical form of the disease:\n\nSymptoms:\n\nYellow Pustules: The disease manifests initially as small, yellow pustules on the undersides of coffee leaves. These pustules contain masses of spores, contributing to the rapid spread of the infection.\nLeaf Lesions: Over time, the upper leaf surface develops lesions, appearing as small, yellow spots that later turn rust-colored. The contrast between the upper and lower leaf surfaces is a characteristic feature of Coffee Leaf Rust.\nPremature Leaf Drop: Severe infections lead to premature leaf drop, significantly impacting the plant's photosynthetic capacity and overall health.\n\nProgression:\n\nRapid Spore Production: The fungus undergoes rapid spore production within the pustules, facilitating the widespread dissemination of infectious spores under favorable conditions.\nSecondary Infections: Secondary infections can occur, exacerbating the damage to coffee plants and contributing to the rapid progression of the disease.\n\nSpread and Survival:\n\nWind Dissemination: Coffee Leaf Rust is primarily spread by wind, with spores carried over long distances to infect nearby coffee plants.\nSurvival on Alternate Hosts: The fungus can also survive on alternative hosts, contributing to its persistence even in the absence of coffee plants.\n\nFavorable Conditions:\n\nWarm Temperatures: Coffee Leaf Rust thrives in warm climates, with optimal temperature ranges between 20 to 24 degrees Celsius.\nRainfall: Adequate rainfall, coupled with high humidity, creates favorable conditions for the initiation and spread of the disease.\n\nManagement and Control:\n\nFungicides: The application of effective fungicides is a key component of managing Coffee Leaf Rust. Timely and targeted treatments are crucial to prevent and control the disease.\nResistant Varieties: Planting coffee varieties that demonstrate resistance to Coffee Leaf Rust is a proactive measure to mitigate the impact of the disease.\nPruning: Pruning infected branches and removing heavily affected leaves can help reduce the disease's severity and limit its spread.\nQuarantine Measures: Implementing quarantine measures to prevent the movement of infected plant material can be crucial in containing the disease's spread.\nRegular Monitoring: Regular and systematic monitoring of coffee plantations is essential for early detection of Coffee Leaf Rust, enabling prompt intervention.\n\nConclusion:\n\nCritical Coffee Leaf Rust is a formidable threat to coffee cultivation, capable of causing significant economic losses. Swift and coordinated management strategies, incorporating fungicides, resistant varieties, and cultural practices, are essential for preserving the health and productivity of coffee plants. Vigilance, research-based approaches, and collaboration within the coffee industry are paramount to effectively combatting the impact of this devastating disease."
            android:textColor="@color/green"
            android:textStyle="bold" />


    </ScrollView>

    <!-- TextView for the description -->

    <FrameLayout
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="48dp"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        tools:ignore="ExtraText">

        <!-- White border -->
        <View
            android:layout_width="320dp"
            android:layout_height="220dp"
            android:background="@android:color/white"/> <!-- Adjust the width to control the border size -->
        <!-- Adjust the height to control the border size -->


        <!-- Original ImageView with content -->
        <ImageView
            android:id="@+id/imageViewMild"
            android:layout_width="300dp"
            android:layout_height="200dp"
            android:layout_gravity="center"
            android:scaleType="centerCrop"
            android:src="@drawable/leafrustcrit" />
    </FrameLayout>


    <!-- Back Button -->



    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView43"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_alignParentTop="true"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="9dp"
        android:fontFamily="@font/hammersmith_one"
        android:text="Critical Leaf Rust"
        android:textColor="@color/white"
        android:textSize="25sp"
        android:textStyle="bold" />

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView44"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="300dp"
        android:fontFamily="@font/hammersmith_one"
        android:text="Description"
        android:textColor="@color/green"
        android:textSize="25sp"
        android:textStyle="bold" />


</RelativeLayout>
