<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:background="#00704a"
    tools:context=".SootyMoldMild">

    <!-- ImageView for the picture -->

    <ImageView
        android:id="@+id/imageView26"
        android:layout_width="449dp"
        android:layout_height="430dp"
        android:layout_alignParentStart="true"
        android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
        android:background="@drawable/whitebg2"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="0.0"
        tools:ignore="MissingConstraints" />

    <ScrollView
        android:id="@+id/scrollView2"
        android:layout_width="327dp"
        android:layout_height="351dp"
        android:layout_alignParentTop="true"
        android:layout_alignParentEnd="true"
        android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="340dp"
        android:layout_marginEnd="2dp"
        android:layout_marginBottom="40dp"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="0.936">

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="300dp"
            android:layout_height="600dp"
            android:fontFamily="@font/hammersmith_one"
            android:justificationMode="inter_word"
            android:text="Mild Coffee Leaf Sooty Molds disease, caused by various sooty mold fungi, is a prevalent issue affecting coffee plants. Here is a description of the mild form of the disease:\n\nSymptoms:\n\nSooty Coating: The mild form of Coffee Leaf Sooty Molds disease manifests as a dark, sooty coating on the surfaces of leaves, stems, and other plant parts.\n\nLeaf Discoloration: Affected leaves may exhibit discoloration, appearing darkened or blackened due to the presence of the sooty molds.\n\nReduced Photosynthesis: As the disease progresses, the sooty mold layer interferes with photosynthesis, potentially leading to reduced energy production within the plant.\n\nAnt Presence: The mild infection may attract ants, as they are known to feed on the sugary secretions produced by certain sooty mold fungi.\n\nProgression:\n\nSpread: The sooty molds can spread from plant to plant, especially in conditions where honeydew-producing insects like aphids are present.\n\nEnvironmental Influence: Environmental factors, such as high humidity and the presence of honeydew-producing insects, contribute to the spread and persistence of the disease.\n\nImpact on Plant Health: While the mild form may not cause severe harm, unchecked infections can compromise overall plant health.\n\nSpread and Survival:\n\nTransmission: The primary mode of transmission is through honeydew-producing insects, such as aphids, which carry fungal spores from plant to plant.\n\nSurvival: The sooty molds can survive on the sugary excretions and plant surfaces, providing a continuous source for new infections.\n\nFavorable Conditions:\n\nInsect Presence: The presence of honeydew-producing insects, which serve as vectors, creates favorable conditions for the establishment and spread of Coffee Leaf Sooty Molds.\n\nEnvironmental Factors: High humidity and warm temperatures further enhance the suitability of the environment for the disease.\n\nManagement and Control:\n\nInsect Control: Controlling honeydew-producing insects through insecticides or biological control measures is a fundamental aspect of disease management.\n\nAnt Control: Managing ant populations, which protect honeydew-producing insects, contributes to the control of sooty mold spread.\n\nPruning: Removing heavily affected plant parts, such as leaves and stems, aids in reducing the disease's impact.\n\nFungicides: In severe cases, targeted fungicides may be considered to control the sooty mold fungi.\n\nCultural Practices: Implementing cultural practices that discourage honeydew-producing insects and promote a healthy plant environment is essential for long-term disease control.\n\nRegular Monitoring:\n\nVisual Inspection: Regularly inspecting plants for signs of sooty mold growth, honeydew-producing insects, and ant activity allows for early detection.\n\nPrompt Action: Swift action upon detecting mild infections helps prevent the escalation of the disease and minimizes its impact on coffee plants.\n\nConclusion:\n\nMild Coffee Leaf Sooty Molds disease, although less damaging in its initial stages, requires proactive management to prevent widespread infection. Control measures targeting honeydew-producing insects, ant populations, and environmental factors contribute to preserving the health and productivity of coffee plants. Regular monitoring and timely interventions are crucial components of an effective strategy against this fungal disease."
            android:textColor="@color/green"
            android:textStyle="bold" />


    </ScrollView>

    <!-- TextView for the description -->

    <FrameLayout
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="48dp"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        tools:ignore="ExtraText">

        <!-- White border -->
        <View
            android:layout_width="320dp"
            android:layout_height="220dp"
            android:background="@android:color/white"/> <!-- Adjust the width to control the border size -->
        <!-- Adjust the height to control the border size -->


        <!-- Original ImageView with content -->
        <ImageView
            android:id="@+id/imageViewMild"
            android:layout_width="300dp"
            android:layout_height="200dp"
            android:layout_gravity="center"
            android:scaleType="centerCrop"
            android:src="@drawable/sootymoldmild" />
    </FrameLayout>


    <!-- Back Button -->



    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView43"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_alignParentTop="true"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="9dp"
        android:fontFamily="@font/hammersmith_one"
        android:text="Mild Sooty Molds"
        android:textColor="@color/white"
        android:textSize="25sp"
        android:textStyle="bold" />

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView44"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="300dp"
        android:fontFamily="@font/hammersmith_one"
        android:text="Description"
        android:textColor="@color/green"
        android:textSize="25sp"
        android:textStyle="bold" />


</RelativeLayout>
