<!-- activity_cercospora_mild.xml -->
<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:background="#00704a"
    tools:context=".PhomaMod">

    <!-- ImageView for the picture -->

    <ImageView
        android:id="@+id/imageView26"
        android:layout_width="449dp"
        android:layout_height="430dp"
        android:layout_alignParentStart="true"
        android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
        android:background="@drawable/whitebg2"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="0.0"
        tools:ignore="MissingConstraints" />

    <ScrollView
        android:id="@+id/scrollView2"
        android:layout_width="327dp"
        android:layout_height="351dp"
        android:layout_alignParentTop="true"
        android:layout_alignParentEnd="true"
        android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="340dp"
        android:layout_marginEnd="2dp"
        android:layout_marginBottom="40dp"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="0.936">

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="300dp"
            android:layout_height="600dp"
            android:fontFamily="@font/hammersmith_one"
            android:justificationMode="inter_word"
            android:text="Moderate Coffee Leaf Phoma Disease, caused by the fungus belonging to the Phoma genus, is a notable fungal infection impacting coffee plants. Here is a detailed description of the moderate form of the disease:\n\nSymptoms:\n\nLesions: Similar to the mild form, the disease initiates with the appearance of small, yellowish lesions on the leaves of coffee plants.\nSpot Formation: These lesions progress into circular or angular brown spots on the leaves as the infection advances.\nColor Variation: The spots may exhibit variations in color, presenting hues of brown or tan, contributing to the distinctive appearance of the infected foliage.\nNecrotic Areas: Severe infections may result in the development of necrotic areas within the lesions, further compromising the health of the affected leaves.\n\nProgression:\n\nLesion Expansion: The lesions gradually enlarge over time, and in moderate cases, they might merge, forming larger irregular-shaped spots on the leaves.\nLeaf Deterioration: Prolonged infection can lead to the deterioration of leaves, causing them to wither and drop prematurely from the coffee plant.\n\nSpread and Survival:\n\nMeans of Spread: Similar to the mild variant, the fungus causing Moderate Coffee Leaf Phoma Disease can spread through mechanisms such as wind, rain splashes, or contamination via tools.\nSurvival: The fungus has the capacity to persist on infected plant debris, contributing to the sustained presence of the disease within the coffee plantation.\n\nFavorable Conditions:\n\nEnvironmental Factors: High humidity, frequent rain, and warm temperatures create favorable conditions for the development and progression of Moderate Coffee Leaf Phoma Disease.\n\nManagement and Control:\n\nIntegrated Approach: Effectively managing the disease involves a comprehensive strategy encompassing both cultural and chemical control measures.\nPruning: Pruning practices, particularly the removal of infected leaves, constitute a critical step in controlling the spread of the disease.\nFungicides: The application of targeted fungicides, selected based on their efficacy against the specific Phoma fungus, can prove effective in disease management.\nCultural Practices: Enhancing cultural practices, such as optimizing humidity levels and improving air circulation, plays a crucial role in disease prevention.\nPlant Health: Maintaining overall plant health through appropriate nutrition and care remains paramount for enhancing the plant's resistance against Moderate Coffee Leaf Phoma Disease.\nMonitoring: Regular monitoring and early detection are imperative for the timely implementation of control measures.\n\nConsultation:\n\nExpert Guidance: Consulting with agricultural specialists or plant pathologists is essential for obtaining tailored guidance on control strategies, considering the severity of the infection and local environmental conditions.\n\nConclusion:\n\nModerate Coffee Leaf Phoma Disease poses a significant threat to coffee plants, potentially leading to leaf deterioration and diminished yield if not adequately managed. A proactive approach involving cultural practices, vigilant monitoring, and strategic control measures is crucial for mitigating the impact of this disease on coffee plantations."
            android:textColor="@color/green"
            android:textStyle="bold" />


    </ScrollView>

    <!-- TextView for the description -->

    <FrameLayout
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="48dp"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        tools:ignore="ExtraText">

        <!-- White border -->
        <View
            android:layout_width="320dp"
            android:layout_height="220dp"
            android:background="@android:color/white"/> <!-- Adjust the width to control the border size -->
        <!-- Adjust the height to control the border size -->


        <!-- Original ImageView with content -->
        <ImageView
            android:id="@+id/imageViewMild"
            android:layout_width="300dp"
            android:layout_height="200dp"
            android:layout_gravity="center"
            android:scaleType="centerCrop"
            android:src="@drawable/phomamoderate" />
    </FrameLayout>


    <!-- Back Button -->



    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView43"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_alignParentTop="true"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="9dp"
        android:fontFamily="@font/hammersmith_one"
        android:text="Moderate Phoma"
        android:textColor="@color/white"
        android:textSize="25sp"
        android:textStyle="bold" />

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView44"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="300dp"
        android:fontFamily="@font/hammersmith_one"
        android:text="Description"
        android:textColor="@color/green"
        android:textSize="25sp"
        android:textStyle="bold" />


</RelativeLayout>
