<!-- activity_cercospora_mild.xml -->
<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:background="#00704a"
    tools:context=".LeafMinerCrit">

    <!-- ImageView for the picture -->

    <ImageView
        android:id="@+id/imageView26"
        android:layout_width="449dp"
        android:layout_height="430dp"
        android:layout_alignParentStart="true"
        android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
        android:background="@drawable/whitebg2"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="0.0"
        tools:ignore="MissingConstraints" />

    <ScrollView
        android:id="@+id/scrollView2"
        android:layout_width="327dp"
        android:layout_height="351dp"
        android:layout_alignParentTop="true"
        android:layout_alignParentEnd="true"
        android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="340dp"
        android:layout_marginEnd="2dp"
        android:layout_marginBottom="40dp"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="0.936">

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="300dp"
            android:layout_height="600dp"
            android:fontFamily="@font/hammersmith_one"
            android:justificationMode="inter_word"
            android:text="Critical Coffee Leaf Miner disease, caused by the Coffee Leaf Miner (CLM) insect, represents a severe threat to coffee plants. Here is a comprehensive description of the critical form of the disease:\n\nSymptoms:\n\nLeaf Mining: The primary symptom of Critical Coffee Leaf Miner disease is the presence of irregular, winding tunnels or mines created by the larvae of the Coffee Leaf Miner within the coffee plant leaves.\n\nWhite or Silvery Trails: These tunnels often appear as white or silvery trails on the surface of the leaves, indicating the destructive feeding activity of the larvae.\n\nLeaf Necrosis: As the infestation progresses, affected leaves may exhibit necrotic areas surrounding the tunnels, leading to a decline in the overall health of the plant.\n\nPremature Leaf Drop: Severe infestations can result in premature leaf drop, significantly impacting the plant's ability to photosynthesize and compromising its vitality.\n\nLife Cycle:\n\nEgg Deposition: The adult Coffee Leaf Miner female lays eggs on the undersides of coffee plant leaves.\n\nLarval Feeding: Upon hatching, the larvae tunnel into the leaves, feeding on the inner tissues and creating the characteristic mines.\n\nPupal Stage: Larvae pupate within the mines before emerging as adults, completing the life cycle and perpetuating the infestation.\n\nSpread and Infestation:\n\nFlight: Adult Coffee Leaf Miners are capable of flight, facilitating the spread of the infestation to neighboring coffee plants.\n\nWind Dispersal: Wind can carry the newly emerged adults to new locations, contributing to the wide distribution of the Coffee Leaf Miner.\n\nContaminated Equipment: Infested plant material and contaminated equipment can serve as additional sources of infestation.\n\nEnvironmental Factors:\n\nTemperature: Critical Coffee Leaf Miner disease is favored by moderate temperatures, and its impact can intensify under conditions of optimal warmth.\n\nAltitude: The disease is known to affect coffee plants at various altitudes, posing a challenge to coffee cultivation across diverse regions.\n\nManagement and Control:\n\nBiological Control: Introducing natural predators of the Coffee Leaf Miner, such as parasitoid wasps, can help in biological control.\n\nChemical Control: In severe cases, targeted application of insecticides specifically formulated for Coffee Leaf Miner control may be necessary.\n\nMonitoring: Regular monitoring for early signs of infestation, including leaf mines and adult presence, is crucial for timely intervention.\n\nQuarantine Measures: Implementing quarantine measures to prevent the movement of infested plant material and equipment can aid in disease containment.\n\nConclusion:\n\nCritical Coffee Leaf Miner disease poses a significant threat to coffee plantations worldwide. Effective management strategies, including biological and chemical controls, alongside vigilant monitoring, are essential to mitigate the impact of this destructive insect infestation and safeguard the health of coffee plants. Consultation with entomologists and agricultural experts is advised for tailored control measures based on the severity of the infestation and regional conditions."
            android:textColor="@color/green"
            android:textStyle="bold" />


    </ScrollView>

    <!-- TextView for the description -->

    <FrameLayout
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="48dp"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        tools:ignore="ExtraText">

        <!-- White border -->
        <View
            android:layout_width="320dp"
            android:layout_height="220dp"
            android:background="@android:color/white"/> <!-- Adjust the width to control the border size -->
        <!-- Adjust the height to control the border size -->


        <!-- Original ImageView with content -->
        <ImageView
            android:id="@+id/imageViewMild"
            android:layout_width="300dp"
            android:layout_height="200dp"
            android:layout_gravity="center"
            android:scaleType="centerCrop"
            android:src="@drawable/leafminercrit" />
    </FrameLayout>


    <!-- Back Button -->



    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView43"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_alignParentTop="true"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="9dp"
        android:fontFamily="@font/hammersmith_one"
        android:text="Critical Leaf Miner"
        android:textColor="@color/white"
        android:textSize="25sp"
        android:textStyle="bold" />

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView44"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="300dp"
        android:fontFamily="@font/hammersmith_one"
        android:text="Description"
        android:textColor="@color/green"
        android:textSize="25sp"
        android:textStyle="bold" />


</RelativeLayout>
