<!-- activity_cercospora_mild.xml -->
<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:background="#00704a"
    tools:context=".CercosporaMild">

    <!-- ImageView for the picture -->

    <ImageView
        android:id="@+id/imageView26"
        android:layout_width="449dp"
        android:layout_height="430dp"
        android:layout_alignParentStart="true"
        android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
        android:background="@drawable/whitebg2"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="0.0"
        tools:ignore="MissingConstraints" />

    <ScrollView
        android:id="@+id/scrollView2"
        android:layout_width="327dp"
        android:layout_height="351dp"
        android:layout_alignParentTop="true"
        android:layout_alignParentEnd="true"
        android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="340dp"
        android:layout_marginEnd="2dp"
        android:layout_marginBottom="40dp"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="0.936">

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="300dp"
            android:layout_height="600dp"
            android:fontFamily="@font/hammersmith_one"
            android:justificationMode="inter_word"
            android:textColor="@color/green"
            android:text="Coffee leaf cercospora, caused by the fungus Cercospora coffeicola, is a significant fungal disease that affects coffee plants. Here's a description of the critical aspects of the coffee leaf cercospora disease:\n\n1. Identification:\n\nSymptoms: Critical infections of coffee leaf cercospora are characterized by the appearance of circular or angular brown spots on the leaves.\nLesion Development: The disease typically starts with small, yellowish lesions that gradually enlarge and turn brown.\nBorder Characteristics: Lesions may have a reddish or purplish border and can coalesce, forming larger irregular-shaped spots.\nLeaf Distortion: As the disease progresses, the affected leaves may become distorted, dry out, and eventually fall off.\n\n2. Severity and Impact:\n\nDefoliation: Severe infections can lead to significant defoliation, impacting the overall health and productivity of coffee plants.\nReduced Photosynthesis: The disease can reduce photosynthesis efficiency, affecting the plant's ability to produce energy and nutrients.\nDecreased Yield: Coffee leaf cercospora can lead to a decrease in coffee yield, affecting the quantity and quality of the harvest.\n\n3. Spread and Survival:\n\nFungal Source: The fungus Cercospora coffeicola survives on infected plant debris.\nTransmission: The disease can be spread through various means, including wind, rain splashes, or contaminated tools.\nFavorable Conditions: Coffee leaf cercospora thrives in conditions of high humidity, frequent rain, and warm temperatures.\n\n4. Management and Control:\n\nCultural Control: Cultural practices such as pruning and removing infected leaves help manage the disease.\nChemical Control: Applying appropriate fungicides can be part of the management strategy.\nEnvironmental Practices: Improving cultural practices to reduce humidity and improve air circulation can contribute to disease control.\nOverall Plant Health: Maintaining the overall health of coffee plants through proper nutrition and care is crucial.\n\n5. Monitoring and Early Detection:\n\nRegular Monitoring: Regular monitoring of coffee plants for symptoms helps in early detection.\nConsultation: Consulting with agricultural specialists or plant pathologists is valuable for effective control strategies.\nAdaptation: Control strategies may need to be adapted based on the severity of infection and local conditions.\n\n6. Prevention:\n\nCleanliness: Keeping the plantation clean by removing infected debris helps prevent the spread of the disease.\nIsolation: Isolating infected plants and avoiding the introduction of contaminated material is essential for prevention.\n\nUnderstanding the characteristics and management strategies for critical coffee leaf cercospora disease is crucial for coffee growers to protect their crops and maintain a healthy and productive coffee plantation."
            android:textStyle="bold" />
    </ScrollView>

    <ImageView
        android:id="@+id/imageViewMild"
        android:layout_width="300dp"
        android:layout_height="200dp"
        android:src="@drawable/cercosporacritical"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:scaleType="centerCrop"
        android:layout_marginTop="70dp"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent" />

    <!-- TextView for the description -->



    <!-- Back Button -->

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView43"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="26dp"
        android:fontFamily="@font/hammersmith_one"
        android:text="Critical Cercospora"
        android:textColor="@color/white"
        android:textSize="25sp"
        android:textStyle="bold" />

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView44"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="300dp"
        android:fontFamily="@font/hammersmith_one"
        android:text="Description"
        android:textColor="@color/green"
        android:textSize="25sp"
        android:textStyle="bold" />


</RelativeLayout>
