<!-- activity_cercospora_mild.xml -->
<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:background="#00704a"
    tools:context=".LeafMinerMod">

    <!-- ImageView for the picture -->

    <ImageView
        android:id="@+id/imageView26"
        android:layout_width="449dp"
        android:layout_height="430dp"
        android:layout_alignParentStart="true"
        android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
        android:background="@drawable/whitebg2"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="0.0"
        tools:ignore="MissingConstraints" />

    <ScrollView
        android:id="@+id/scrollView2"
        android:layout_width="327dp"
        android:layout_height="351dp"
        android:layout_alignParentTop="true"
        android:layout_alignParentEnd="true"
        android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="340dp"
        android:layout_marginEnd="2dp"
        android:layout_marginBottom="40dp"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="0.936">

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="300dp"
            android:layout_height="600dp"
            android:fontFamily="@font/hammersmith_one"
            android:justificationMode="inter_word"
            android:text="Moderate Coffee Leaf Miner Disease, caused by the Coffee Leaf Miner (CLM) insect, is a plant ailment that affects coffee crops. Here is a detailed description of the moderate form of the disease:\n\nSymptoms:\n\nLeaf Mining: The disease initiates with the presence of small, serpentine mines on the leaves, indicating the activity of Coffee Leaf Miner larvae.\nYellowing of Leaves: Infested leaves exhibit yellowing, a consequence of the feeding activities of the larvae within the leaf tissues.\nLeaf Curling: Moderate infections may lead to the curling of leaves as the larvae disrupt normal leaf development during their feeding.\nPresence of Larvae: Examination of affected leaves may reveal the presence of Coffee Leaf Miner larvae within the mines, further confirming the diagnosis.\n\nProgression:\n\nIncreased Mining Activity: Over time, the mining activity intensifies, with larvae creating more extensive and interconnected mines within the leaves.\nStunted Growth: Infested plants may exhibit stunted growth due to the impact of the larvae on the plant's ability to photosynthesize and transport nutrients.\nPremature Leaf Drop: Moderate infections can result in premature leaf drop, affecting the overall health and vitality of the coffee plant.\n\nSpread and Survival:\n\nFlight of Adult Insects: Coffee Leaf Miners can spread by the flight of adult insects, which may carry the disease to neighboring plants.\nPupal Stage Survival: The pupal stage of the Coffee Leaf Miner allows it to survive in the soil, contributing to the persistence of the disease between growing seasons.\n\nFavorable Conditions:\n\nTemperature: Moderate temperatures are conducive to the development and proliferation of Coffee Leaf Miner infestations.\nPlant Density: High plant density can facilitate the spread of the disease as adult insects move easily between closely spaced plants.\n\nManagement and Control:\n\nBiological Control: Introduction of natural predators or parasites of Coffee Leaf Miner can help in biological control.\nChemical Control: The use of insecticides targeted at the larval stage can be effective in managing moderate infestations.\nPruning: Pruning affected branches and promptly removing infested leaves can aid in controlling the spread of the disease.\nCultural Practices: Practices such as maintaining proper spacing between plants and promoting overall plant health contribute to disease resistance.\n\nRegular Monitoring:\n\nVisual Inspections: Regular visual inspections of coffee plants are crucial for early detection of Coffee Leaf Miner activity.\nMonitoring Traps: Employing pheromone traps can assist in monitoring adult insect populations, aiding in timely intervention.\n\nConsultation:\n\nEntomologists: Consulting with entomologists or agricultural extension services can provide valuable insights into tailored control strategies based on the severity of infestation and local conditions.\n\nConclusion:\n\nModerate Coffee Leaf Miner Disease poses a significant threat to coffee plants, affecting their growth and productivity. Integrated pest management strategies, including biological control, chemical interventions, and vigilant monitoring, are pivotal for mitigating the impact of this disease on coffee crops. Early detection and a holistic approach to disease management are essential for preserving the health and yield of coffee plants."
            android:textColor="@color/green"
            android:textStyle="bold" />


    </ScrollView>

    <!-- TextView for the description -->

    <FrameLayout
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="48dp"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        tools:ignore="ExtraText">

        <!-- White border -->
        <View
            android:layout_width="320dp"
            android:layout_height="220dp"
            android:background="@android:color/white"/> <!-- Adjust the width to control the border size -->
        <!-- Adjust the height to control the border size -->


        <!-- Original ImageView with content -->
        <ImageView
            android:id="@+id/imageViewMild"
            android:layout_width="300dp"
            android:layout_height="200dp"
            android:layout_gravity="center"
            android:scaleType="centerCrop"
            android:src="@drawable/leafminermod" />
    </FrameLayout>


    <!-- Back Button -->



    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView43"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_alignParentTop="true"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="9dp"
        android:fontFamily="@font/hammersmith_one"
        android:text="Moderate Leaf Miner"
        android:textColor="@color/white"
        android:textSize="25sp"
        android:textStyle="bold" />

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView44"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="300dp"
        android:fontFamily="@font/hammersmith_one"
        android:text="Description"
        android:textColor="@color/green"
        android:textSize="25sp"
        android:textStyle="bold" />


</RelativeLayout>
