<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:background="#00704a"
    tools:context=".LeafRustMod">

    <!-- ImageView for the picture -->

    <ImageView
        android:id="@+id/imageView26"
        android:layout_width="449dp"
        android:layout_height="430dp"
        android:layout_alignParentStart="true"
        android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
        android:background="@drawable/whitebg2"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="0.0"
        tools:ignore="MissingConstraints" />

    <ScrollView
        android:id="@+id/scrollView2"
        android:layout_width="327dp"
        android:layout_height="351dp"
        android:layout_alignParentTop="true"
        android:layout_alignParentEnd="true"
        android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="340dp"
        android:layout_marginEnd="2dp"
        android:layout_marginBottom="40dp"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="0.936">

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="300dp"
            android:layout_height="600dp"
            android:fontFamily="@font/hammersmith_one"
            android:justificationMode="inter_word"
            android:text="Moderate Coffee Leaf Rust disease, caused by the fungus Hemileia vastatrix, is a significant threat to coffee plants. Here is a description of the moderate form of the disease:\n\nSymptoms:\n\nPustules: The disease initiates with the appearance of yellowish-orange pustules on the underside of coffee leaves. These pustules contain masses of rust-colored spores.\nLeaf Chlorosis: As the infection progresses, infected leaves exhibit chlorosis, resulting in a yellowing of the foliage. This is indicative of the disruption of chlorophyll production.\nReduced Bean Quality: In addition to affecting leaves, moderate Coffee Leaf Rust can lead to a decrease in the quality of coffee beans, impacting both appearance and taste.\n\nProgression:\n\nSystemic Infection: Unlike the mild form, moderate Coffee Leaf Rust involves systemic infection, affecting various parts of the plant beyond the leaves.\nBranch and Stem Lesions: The fungus can cause lesions on branches and stems, potentially leading to dieback in severe cases.\n\nSpread and Survival:\n\nAerial Transmission: Hemileia vastatrix primarily spreads through aerial transmission of spores carried by wind. The microscopic spores can travel over considerable distances.\nSurvival on Alternate Hosts: The fungus may survive on alternate hosts, contributing to its persistence even in the absence of coffee plants.\n\nFavorable Conditions:\n\nHumidity and Rainfall: High humidity and frequent rainfall create optimal conditions for the proliferation of moderate Coffee Leaf Rust.\nModerate Temperatures: Moderate temperatures, typically ranging from 20 to 24 degrees Celsius, facilitate the development and spread of the disease.\n\nManagement and Control:\n\nResistant Varieties: Planting coffee varieties with resistance to Coffee Leaf Rust is a key preventive measure.\nFungicides: Application of fungicides, especially those containing active ingredients effective against Hemileia vastatrix, can help manage the disease.\nPruning and Sanitation: Pruning affected branches and removing infected leaves are crucial for preventing the spread of the fungus.\n\nConsultation:\n\nResearch Institutions: Collaboration with agricultural research institutions can provide insights into the latest developments in Coffee Leaf Rust management.\nSpecialized Advice: Seeking guidance from plant pathologists and experts specializing in coffee diseases is essential for developing effective control strategies.\n\nConclusion:\n\nModerate Coffee Leaf Rust poses a serious threat to coffee plantations due to its systemic nature and potential impact on bean quality. Implementing a combination of resistant varieties, fungicides, and vigilant sanitation practices is crucial for mitigating the detrimental effects of this disease on coffee crops."
            android:textColor="@color/green"
            android:textStyle="bold" />


    </ScrollView>

    <!-- TextView for the description -->

    <FrameLayout
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="48dp"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        tools:ignore="ExtraText">

        <!-- White border -->
        <View
            android:layout_width="320dp"
            android:layout_height="220dp"
            android:background="@android:color/white"/> <!-- Adjust the width to control the border size -->
        <!-- Adjust the height to control the border size -->


        <!-- Original ImageView with content -->
        <ImageView
            android:id="@+id/imageViewMild"
            android:layout_width="300dp"
            android:layout_height="200dp"
            android:layout_gravity="center"
            android:scaleType="centerCrop"
            android:src="@drawable/leafrustmod" />
    </FrameLayout>


    <!-- Back Button -->



    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView43"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_alignParentTop="true"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="9dp"
        android:fontFamily="@font/hammersmith_one"
        android:text="Moderate Leaf Rust"
        android:textColor="@color/white"
        android:textSize="25sp"
        android:textStyle="bold" />

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView44"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="300dp"
        android:fontFamily="@font/hammersmith_one"
        android:text="Description"
        android:textColor="@color/green"
        android:textSize="25sp"
        android:textStyle="bold" />


</RelativeLayout>
