<!-- activity_cercospora_mild.xml -->
<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:background="#00704a"
    tools:context=".PhomaCrit">

    <!-- ImageView for the picture -->

    <ImageView
        android:id="@+id/imageView26"
        android:layout_width="449dp"
        android:layout_height="430dp"
        android:layout_alignParentStart="true"
        android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
        android:background="@drawable/whitebg2"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="0.0"
        tools:ignore="MissingConstraints" />

    <ScrollView
        android:id="@+id/scrollView2"
        android:layout_width="327dp"
        android:layout_height="351dp"
        android:layout_alignParentTop="true"
        android:layout_alignParentEnd="true"
        android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="340dp"
        android:layout_marginEnd="2dp"
        android:layout_marginBottom="40dp"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="0.936">

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="300dp"
            android:layout_height="600dp"
            android:fontFamily="@font/hammersmith_one"
            android:justificationMode="inter_word"
            android:text="Critical Coffee Leaf Phoma Disease, caused by the pathogenic fungus Phoma spp., is a severe and potentially devastating affliction affecting coffee plants. Here is a detailed description of the critical form of the disease:\n\nSymptoms:\n\nNecrotic Lesions: The disease manifests initially with small, necrotic lesions on coffee plant leaves, appearing as dark brown to black spots.\nRapid Spread: Unlike the mild form, Critical Coffee Leaf Phoma Disease exhibits rapid lesion expansion, covering extensive leaf surfaces within a short period.\nDark Lesion Centers: Lesions develop a characteristic dark center, surrounded by a zone of varying discoloration, creating a stark and noticeable contrast on affected leaves.\nPremature Leaf Drop: Severely infected leaves undergo premature senescence and drop prematurely, significantly impacting the plant's foliage and overall health.\nStem Lesions: In advanced stages, the disease may progress to affect stems, causing cankers and lesions that compromise the structural integrity of the plant.\n\nProgression:\n\nRapid Progression: The disease progresses swiftly, causing extensive damage to leaves and stems, leading to a rapid decline in plant health.\nCanker Formation: Stem lesions can coalesce, forming larger cankers that weaken the plant's vascular system, hindering nutrient and water transport.\nPlant Death: In severe cases, Critical Coffee Leaf Phoma Disease can lead to plant death, resulting in complete crop loss.\n\nSpread and Survival:\n\nWind Dissemination: The fungal spores responsible for the disease are disseminated by wind, contributing to the rapid spread of the infection.\nContaminated Equipment: Human activities, such as the use of contaminated pruning tools or equipment, can facilitate the transmission of the pathogen.\nSurvival in Debris: Phoma spp. can survive in infected plant debris, serving as a source of inoculum for subsequent infections.\n\nFavorable Conditions:\n\nMoisture: High humidity and frequent rain provide optimal conditions for the proliferation and spread of Critical Coffee Leaf Phoma Disease.\nTemperature: The disease is favored by moderate to warm temperatures, promoting the rapid multiplication of the pathogen.\n\nManagement and Control:\n\nFungicidal Intervention: Given the severity of the disease, the application of potent fungicides is crucial for mitigating its impact. Fungicides with systemic action are often recommended for better control.\nStrict Sanitation Measures: Implementing rigorous sanitation practices, including the prompt removal and destruction of infected plant material, is essential to prevent the disease's persistence.\nIsolation: Isolating and quarantining affected plants can prevent the further spread of the disease within a coffee plantation.\nProfessional Consultation: Engaging with agricultural specialists or plant pathologists is imperative for the development of an effective and tailored management strategy based on the specific characteristics of the pathogen and local conditions.\n\nConclusion:\n\nCritical Coffee Leaf Phoma Disease poses a significant threat to coffee plants, leading to rapid and extensive damage. Timely intervention, through the application of appropriate fungicides and strict sanitation measures, is paramount for preventing widespread devastation and preserving the health of coffee crops. Collaborating with experts in the field is essential for implementing effective control measures and minimizing the economic impact on coffee production."
            android:textColor="@color/green"
            android:textStyle="bold" />


    </ScrollView>

    <!-- TextView for the description -->

    <FrameLayout
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="48dp"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        tools:ignore="ExtraText">

        <!-- White border -->
        <View
            android:layout_width="320dp"
            android:layout_height="220dp"
            android:background="@android:color/white"/> <!-- Adjust the width to control the border size -->
        <!-- Adjust the height to control the border size -->


        <!-- Original ImageView with content -->
        <ImageView
            android:id="@+id/imageViewMild"
            android:layout_width="300dp"
            android:layout_height="200dp"
            android:layout_gravity="center"
            android:scaleType="centerCrop"
            android:src="@drawable/phomacritical" />
    </FrameLayout>


    <!-- Back Button -->



    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView43"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_alignParentTop="true"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="9dp"
        android:fontFamily="@font/hammersmith_one"
        android:text="Critical Phoma"
        android:textColor="@color/white"
        android:textSize="25sp"
        android:textStyle="bold" />

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView44"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="300dp"
        android:fontFamily="@font/hammersmith_one"
        android:text="Description"
        android:textColor="@color/green"
        android:textSize="25sp"
        android:textStyle="bold" />


</RelativeLayout>
