<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout
    xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:orientation="vertical"
    android:padding="16dp">

    <TextView
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:text="Term of Agreement"
        android:textStyle="bold"
        android:textSize="24sp"
        android:layout_gravity="center"
        android:layout_marginBottom="16dp" />

    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="200dp">

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:textSize="15sp"
            android:justificationMode="inter_word"
            android:text="Terms and Conditions for the Use of Coffeetect Application:\n\n1. Acceptance of Terms: By accessing and using the Coffeetect application, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions set forth herein.\n\n2. Application Purpose: Coffeetect is designed to assist coffee farmers in identifying and managing diseases affecting coffee leaves, utilizing Digital Image Processing and Convolutional Neural Networks (CNN).\n\n3. Disease Detection: The application utilizes the Convolutional Neural Networks (CNN) algorithm for precise identification of coffee leaf diseases, including rust, phoma, sooty mold, cercospora, and coffee leaf miner. Users can capture or upload images, considering disease severity.\n\n4. Infographic Manual: An infographic manual is provided to users, offering essential guidance on managing detected diseases, facilitating effective disease management strategies.\n\n5. Severity Levels: Disease severity is categorized into three levels: mild, moderate, and critical, assisting farmers in prioritizing and addressing urgent cases.\n\n6. Capture Image and Gallery Upload: Users can capture real-time images or upload existing images for disease detection.\n\n7. Report Visualization and Monthly Report: The application generates tree-specific reports based on the analysis of ten images, aiding in identifying prevalent diseases and assessing severity. Monthly reports, presented in pie graphs, visually represent the diseases detected during that period.\n\n\nLimitations:\n\na. Limited Detection Scope: The application focuses on coffee leaf diseases and does not extend detection to other tree parts.\n\nb. Internet Connection Requirement: Internet access is necessary to view reports and pie graphs.\n\nc. Data Set Accuracy: The application's accuracy depends on the training dataset, which may not be 100% accurate.\n\nd. Image Quality and Lighting: Disease identification may be affected by image quality and lighting conditions. Optimal conditions are recommended for accurate results.\n\n\nUse and Ownership: The Coffeetect application is the intellectual property of the undergraduate fourth-year Bachelor of Science in Information Technology students from CSTC College of Sciences, Technology, and Communication Inc., Sariaya Campus.\n\nModification of Terms: The terms and conditions may be revised without prior notice. Users are responsible for regularly reviewing the terms.\n"
        android:padding="16dp" />


    </ScrollView>

    <CheckBox
        android:id="@+id/checkBox"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:text="I agree to the Terms and Agreement"
        android:layout_gravity="center"
        android:layout_marginTop="16dp" />

</LinearLayout>
